{
    "subject": "Princess_Amalie_of_Hohenzollern-Sigmaringen",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Prince_Eduard_of_Saxe-Altenburg",
    "human_readable": "Princess Amalie of Hohenzollern-Sigmaringen is married to Prince Eduard of Saxe-Altenburg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9846606850624084,
            "question": "What is the name of the Prince who is married to Princess Amalie of Hohenzollern-Sigmaringen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9846324920654297,
            "question": "Who is Princess Amalie of Hohenzollern-Sigmaringen married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8130751848220825,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Princess Amalie and Prince Eduard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7784709930419922,
            "question": "How did the marriage of Princess Amalie and Prince Eduard impact their respective families?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7662997245788574,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Princess Amalie and Prince Eduard's families?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5914358496665955,
            "question": "What is the name of the princely family that Princess Amalie belongs to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4854232966899872,
            "question": "To which royal family does Prince Eduard belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19151468575000763,
            "question": "Who are the spouses in this royal pairing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1187841072678566,
            "question": "What might be some historical events related to their marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10004447400569916,
            "question": "Are there any other known relationships between these families?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Princess Amalie of Hohenzollern-Sigmaringen is married to Prince Eduard of Saxe-Altenburg.",
            "html": "yago_18018_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some historical events related to their marriage?",
            "html": "yago_18018_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the spouses in this royal pairing?",
            "html": "yago_18018_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which royal family does Prince Eduard belong?",
            "html": "yago_18018_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18018_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in the document `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_18018/re-ranker-msmarco/73.txt`, which states that Prince Eduard of Saxe-Altenburg married Princess Amalie of Hohenzollern-Sigmaringen on 25 July 1835."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}